Yours is the life they've chosen.
In Their Skin is a horror, thriller film directed by Jeremy Power Regimbal.
A couple and their young son retreat to their woodland vacation home, only to face
sinister neighbors who intend to kill them and steal their identities.
Mary, played by Selma Blair.
Mark, played by Joshua Close.
Bobby, played by James D'Arcy.
Jane, played by Rachel Miner.
Brendon, played by Quinn Lord.
Jared, played by Alex Ferris.
Skins is a British teen drama television series that follows the lives of a group of
teenagers in Bristol, England, through the two years of sixth form.
Its controversial storylines have explored issues such as dysfunctional families, mental illness (such as depression, eating disorders,
post-traumatic stress disorder, and bipolar disorder), adolescent sexuality, gender, substance abuse, death, and bullying.
Each episode generally focuses on a particular character or subset of characters and the struggles
they face in their lives, with the episodes named after the featured characters.
The show was created by father-and-son television writers Bryan Elsley and Jamie
Brittain for Company Pictures, and premiered on E4 on 25 January 2007.
Skins went on to be a critical success as well as a ratings
winner and has developed a cult following.
It has since been considered revolutionary, and continues to draw appraisal for its depiction of problems
that British youth experience, which was generally not showcased on public TV at the time.
Over its initial six-year run, Skins was atypical of ongoing drama
series in that it replaced its primary cast every two years.
Plans for a film spin-off were first discussed in 2009,
but ultimately did not come to fruition.
Instead, a specially-commissioned seventh and final series of the show was
broadcast in 2013, featuring some of the cast from its 2007–2010 run.
Other ventures to expand the brand have included a short-lived American remake, which aired on MTV in 2011, but was cancelled after
one season after advertisers abandoned the series in response to controversy surrounding the series' sexual content.
The film explores themes of vacation, home invasion, stranger, psycho killer.
The tone is dark and intense.